nitjsr.ac.in 2010-03-09

# :: Welcome to NIT Jamshedpur ::

Thank you for visiting the NIT Jamshedpur web site. NIT Jamshedpur respects your right to privacy and shall protect and respect privacy of its faculty, staff, students, alumni, guest lecturers, participants in inter-college activities and all other visitors who provide personal information by filling out forms and submitting it through this web site. 

Our policy is to collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our web site unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. However, our web servers do automatically recognize some non-personal information such as volume and timing of access as well as the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our site.

Certain personal information that you may voluntarily share with us are your e-mail address, your messages when you communicate electronically with us, information that you provide voluntarily on surveys & other forms or when registering for personalized services. Your information is kept confidential, unaltered, and used only by National Institute of Technology Jamshedpur to administer your request.

Information about your visit is gathered in an aggregate manner for quality control, security and improvement of our site.

NIT Jamshedpur does not disclose or sell any personally identifiable information collected at this site to other companies or organizations. Selected information pertaining to students, faculty members and other visitors, where authorized by you, may be provided to institutions or companies for certain purposes like training programmes, summer projects, research projects, student placement, etc.

Under exceptional circumstances, where the law requires us to do so, we may disclose such information to the Police and Government/Legal authorities.

Should you feel that this Privacy Policy has been violated please write to us.
